唔……这是噩梦么……
与她有关的一切……
明明就在嘴边……
对不起！希儿！
我刚刚说了——
希……儿？
希儿……希儿……希儿！
是的……
那个胆小的你……
那个爱哭鼻子的你……
那个已经比我坚强得多的你！
那个……
我绝不会——
忘记的你！
希儿！！
♪ 我感受到了实数解的触碰 ♪
♪ Here I feel the touch brought by the real number solution. ♪
♪ 两个灵魂的涟漪已到达属于我们的那对狭缝 ♪
♪ Ripples of two souls now have reached our double slits. ♪
♪ 在这世界投射出明暗条带，作为日夜更迭 ♪
♪ Casting stripes of light and dark in the world as days and nights. ♪
♪ 你让我在阳光下自由 ♪
♪ You set me free under the sun. ♪
♪ 我倾愿放飞你的襁褓之梦 ♪
♪ I fly your cradle dreams to the moon and back. ♪
♪ 虫会先化成蝶 ♪
♪ A worm will turn into a butterfly, ♪
♪ 在一个人能找到自我之前 ♪
♪ before one can answer "who am I." ♪
♪ 在冰化成水之后 ♪
♪ After the ice turns into water, ♪
♪ 我倒悬过来的海会成为你的天 ♪
♪ the sea I hang upside down will be your sky. ♪
你找到我了，希儿。
我找到你了，希儿。